floridatrend.com 2016-06-07

# Privacy Policy

**Welcome to FloridaTrend.com.** This website is operated by Trend Magazines Inc. We are committed to protecting personal information about our users and persons who transact business through Web sites we own and operate, including but not limited to: [FloridaTrend. com](http://www.floridatrend.com/), [www.BusinessFlorida.com](http://www.businessflorida.com/), [FloridaSmallBusiness.com](http://www.floridasmallbusiness.com/), [ResearchFlorida.com](http://www.researchflorida.com/) and [FloridaNEXT.com](http://www.floridanext.com/). 

Our postal address is **490 1st Ave. S. , 8th floor, St. Petersburg, FL 33701**. 

We can be reached by email at [webmaster@floridatrend.com](mailto:webmaster@floridatrend.com) or **(727) 821-5800**.

Your use of our websites indicates to us that you have read and accepted this **Privacy Policy** and our Terms and Conditions. 

**Sitewide**

Our web sites use "cookies," an element of data sent and stored on your computer. We use cookies the following ways: In site administration, to complete a user's requested activity, to target specific information, to perform analysis and for research and development. 

Florida Trend may, from time to time, use information you provide as part of the registration process to send you information regarding other products or services from Florida Trend. In addition, Florida Trend may provide aggregated, anonymous statistical information about Florida Trend users to other persons, including potential advertising clients. 

We collect aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and we collect information supplied by those who wish to subscribe to or purchase our print publications. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. 

A user's personally identifying information will not be disclosed to any other party unless otherwise stated prior to collection. Florida Trend accepts no responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties who misuse such information, though Florida Trend will make every effort to pre-screen anyone who requests or purchases this information. 

We cannot control the privacy policies of sites we may link to in our editorial coverage or advertising sections. Therefore, if you provide personal information, including credit card information, to linked third-party sites, the information is stored on their servers and is governed by their privacy policies. 

**Contests, Surveys and Promotions**

In general, we collect two categories of information: (1) information that personally identifies you (for example, your name and address) that you voluntarily supply when you register for an on-line discussion or other site use, or when you subscribe, order, complete a survey, or initiate some other transaction, and (2) non-personally identifying information, which includes information about usage patterns and preferences as users navigate around our sites or use our information services. In some cases, an agent, affiliate, or business partner of Florida Trend collects the information. Third party providers featured on our sites, such as vendors of products and services offered through our sites, may be gathering the same kinds of information. 

WE DO NOT SELL THE NAMES, EMAIL ADDRESSES, OR OTHER PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU ENTER ON OUR SITES TO ANY THIRD PARTIES, INCLUDING ADVERTISERS, UNLESS WE HAVE YOUR PERMISSION TO DO SO, SUCH AS THROUGH A REGISTRATION FOR A CONTEST, SURVEY, OR PARTICULAR SERVICES OR INFORMATION.

From time to time, we or our advertisers may offer contests, sweepstakes, giveaways, or other promotions on our sites. If you enter one of these, you will be asked to provide information about yourself such as your name, address, telephone number and email address so that we or our advertisers can contact you if you win. We may share this information with our corporate affiliates and any co-sponsors of the contest, sweepstakes, give-away, or other promotion. If you do not want us to collect the information requested, to use it to contact you, or to share it, please do not enter any contest, sweepstakes, give-away or promotion.

Contact [webmaster@floridatrend.com](mailto:webmaster@floridatrend.com) (727-821-5800) with questions about this website or additional information regarding the user agreement, copyright or privacy policy. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved. 

**Choices You Have**  
If you wish to discontinue receiving communications from us at any time, please let us know by e-mailing, calling or writing us (see addresses above).
